tapped into the amanda seal show right here high vibrations and this is our community to listen
laugh and learn and we're about to get into it right now with some big up let down let's get
into it amanda who we giving the salute to today's dig up dig up goes to mr star track
barrell williams is the new director of louis vuitton yes the american rapper and producer
that we all know from va and from the neptunes and and from nerb is now the new creative director
for menswear they announced this on instagram and uh they had hired him about 16 months after
the sudden death of its previous menswear designer virgil abloh in 2021 today's
goes to elon musk yeah you heard that jim carrey
elon musk y'all this man threw a tantrum because the super bowl had biden getting a higher amount
of retweets than him yo he did not like that he had less views than the president and so he called an
emergency meeting and threatened to fire his entire team if they didn't create a system that made
everybody see his posts how let down corny lame is that
you